...and after you pass the first three barriers,
you kind of wanna take it all the way.
(Penny:)Well, I'm sorry, Leonard.
It's very hard to feel sympathy for you.
Okay. Let me tell you about the first time
I brought a girl over.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
SHELDON:
Leonard?
(Past Leonard:)Shh. Just pretend we're not here.
[KNOCKING]
SHELDON:
Leonard?
(Past Leonard:)I'm sure he'll go away.
SHELDON: I'm just gonna keep knocking
till you answer.
[KNOCKING]
(Past Sheldon:)Leonard?
Leonard? Leonard?
(Past Leonard:)What do you want?
(Past Leonard:)I didn't say come in.
(Past Sheldon:)You asked what I want.
(Past Sheldon:)I wanted to come in.
(Past Sheldon:)I'm here because you violated
our roommate agreement.
(Past Sheldon:)Specifically, section eight...
...visitor's subsection C, females,
paragraph four, coitus.
"Roommates shall give each other
12 hours notice of impending coitus."
(Past Leonard:)I didn't even know her 12 hours ago.